Up until now, you've been developing the web app
目前为止 你一直在教室或本地开发 Web 应用
However, you can't share the app yet with other people,
但是 你无法与其他人分享该应用
unless you transfer all the files to someone else's computer then have
除非你将所有文件发送到别人的计算机
that person setup a Python environment on his or her local computer.
然后让他/她的自己本地计算机上设置 Python 环境
So, now it's time to deploy the app to
所以 现在应该要将应用部署到
an external server with a web address that anyone can go to to see your work.
带网址的外部服务器 让任何人都可以看到你的工作
There are a lot of companies that provide web servers for deploying a web app.
有很多公司都有提供 Web 服务器 用于部署 Web 应用
In this video, I've chosen to use Heroku,
在这个视频中 我选择使用 Heroku
which is considered a Platform as a Service.
其被视为平台即服务 (PaaS)
In my opinion, it's one of the easier platforms
个人认为 它是比较容易使用的平台
to use and doesn't require much configuration.
并不需要太多配置
There's also a free tier that doesn't expire.
还有一个不会过期的免费套餐
So, if you have a small web app like this one,
所以 如果你有一个像这样的小型 Web 应用
that doesn't have a database,
没有数据库
Heroku will work for our needs.
Heroku 就能满足我们的需求
I'm going to walk you through getting the app up on Heroku,
我将引导你完成在 Heroku 上部署应用
so that you can do it yourself.
这样你就能自己动手操作了
I'm going to do it from the classroom Linux workspace.
从教室 Linux workspace 开始
I'll also provide a list, underneath the video,
我会在视频下方提供一个列表
of other services you can use to put the web app on.
列出你可以使用的其他服务器
Okay. So, this is our web app.
好的 这就是我们的 Web 应用
All of the folders and files are here in the left-hand column.
所有文件夹和文件都在左侧的边栏
My first step is, I'm going to make
第一步是
a new folder and I'm going to put all of these files into that new folder.
创建一个新文件夹 把所有这些文件放入新文件夹中
I'm going to do this from the terminal,
我要用终端来完成以上操作
but you could also do this using the plus sign and
不过你也可以使用加号
also right-clicking on these folders and files here.
还可以在此处右键单击这些文件夹和文件
So, I open a new terminal,
打开一个新的终端
and I'm just going to say,
需要输入的是
make directory, and I'll call it web_app.
mkdir 文件夹名称叫做 web_app
Now, I'm going to move all of these folders and files into this new web app folder.
现在把所有这些文件夹和文件移动到新的 web_app 文件夹中
So, MV is for move,
mv 是 move (移动) 的缩写
-t just means I'm specifying the new directory first and then after that,
-t 意思是 先指定新目录 然后是
all of the files and folders that I want to move into the web app folder.
要移动到 web_app 文件夹的所有文件和文件夹
It looks like I spelled worldbankapp wrong.
看起来拼错了 worldbankapp
So let me just fix that.
修复一下
So, you can see, everything moved over into this new folder.
你可以看到 一切都转移到了这个新文件夹中
So, in order to install this web app,
要安装这个 Web 应用
we're going to have to specify all the python libraries that are needed.
我们必须要指定该应用所需的所有 python 库
Now, in this workspace,
现在 在这个 workspace 中
and probably on your local computer as well,
或者也可能在你的本地计算机上
there are a lot of
安装了很多
extra Python libraries installed that you don't actually need for your web app.
你的 Web 应用实际上不需要的额外 Python 库
So, we're going to deal with this by creating a virtual environment and just
因此 我们要通过创建虚拟环境来解决这个问题
installing all the Python libraries we
在虚拟环境中 只安装这个特定应用所需的 Python 库
Now, this workspace has Anaconda installed,
现在 这个 workspace 安装了 Anaconda
which is a set of tools used for Python and data science.
这是用于 Python 和数据科学的一组工具
There's actually an issue with
目前关于该 Anaconda 安装和 Python 以及虚拟环境存在一个问题
So, first before doing anything,
所以在开始操作之前
you need to run conda update python,
你需要运行 conda update python
and this is going to take a little while.
这需要一段时间
Now, if you don't have Conda installed on your local computer,
如果你没有在本地计算机上安装 Conda
you wouldn't have to do this step.
不用完成这步操作
Okay. And when it says Proceed click
好的 当它显示 Proceed 时 点击 y (代表 yes)
yes and hit Enter and then wait for the installation to finish.
然后按回车 等待安装完成
Okay. Now that Python is updated.
好的 现在 Python 已更新完毕
You can actually make a virtual environment and then start it up.
现在就可以创建一个虚拟环境 然后启动它了
So, to make a virtual environment,
要创建一个虚拟环境
go into the terminal and type the following,
进入终端并输入以下内容
python3 -n venv, and then the name of your virtual environment,
python3 -n venv 然后是你的虚拟环境的名称
which can be anything you want,
可以任意命名
I'm going to call it worldbankenv.
我打算叫做 worldbankenv
Now, you can see there's a new folder up here on the left called
现在 可以看到左侧有一个新文件夹 名为
worldbankenv and inside it's actually a Python installation.
worldbankenv 其中实际上是一个 Python 安装
That's separate from the rest of your Python installation on your computer.
这与你计算机上的其他 Python 安装是分隔开的
The next thing is that you need to activate the virtual environment.
接下来你需要激活虚拟环境
So, I'm going to type in source worldbankenv/bin/activate,
输入 source worldbankenv/bin/activate
and you can see that the virtual environment is activated,
可以看到虚拟环境被激活
because here in the terminal,
因为在终端的这里
now the name of the virtual environment appears.
现在出现了虚拟环境的名称
Okay. The next step is that we're going to pip
好的 下一步是
install the libraries we need for our Flask app.
我们要安装 Flask 应用所需的库
So, again, the reason we're creating
再次提醒 我们创建这个虚拟环境的原因
this virtual environment is that all these libraries are going to
就是要将所有库都安装在该虚拟环境中
the regular Python installation on your local computer.
而不是你本地计算机的常规 Python 安装中
So, pip install.
pip install
Then I'm going to list out all of the libraries I need,
然后列出我需要的所有库
which in this case is Flask, Pandas and Plotly.
在这个示例中是 flask pandas 和 plotly
And then I'm actually going to add in this other library called
然后实际上还要添加一个其他的库
Gunicorn which we're going to need for deploying the web app.
gunicorn 用于部署 Web 应用
Okay. Now from the terminal,
好了 现在在终端中
I am going to go into the web app folder.
我要进入 web_app 文件夹
The next step is to actually install a set of tools that Heroku provides,
下一步是安装 Heroku 提供的一组工具
so that you can write commands and upload your app directly from the terminal to Heroku.
这样你就可以编写命令 将应用直接从终端上传到 Heroku
There's actually a web page that tells
实际上 有一个网页会告诉你
you how to install these tools on different systems.
如何在不同的系统上安装这些工具
This is what it looks like here.
就是这个页面
I'll also put a link to it below the video.
我会在视频下方提供其链接
But on this page,
在这个页面上
it says if you're on a Linux system or Ubuntu system, which we are,
它说如果你在 Linux 或 Ubuntu 系统上(也就是我们当前的系统)
then you're going to do the following,
你要完成以下操作
you go into terminal and you run the following command up here.
进入终端 运行这里的命令
Now it's installing. Just to check that everything installed,
现在就在安装了 为了检查一切安装成功
I'm going to type heroku --version.
输入 heroku --version
Okay. So, it looks like it installed and we're good.
好的 看起来已经安装完毕了
The next thing you're going to want to do is to sign up for a Heroku account.
你要做的下一件事是注册一个 Heroku 帐户
So, it's just like signing up for any other web service.
就像注册任何其他网站的服务一样
If you go to the Heroku website and you click on Sign up here in the top right corner,
访问 Heroku 网站并点击右上角的 Sign up (注册)
you just fill this out with your information.
只需在其中填写你的信息
So, once you've made a username,
当你创建用户名之后
which is just your email address and a password,
也就是你的电子邮件地址 以及密码
you actually need to log in from the command line.
你实际上需要从命令行登录
So, now that we have the Heroku tools installed,
现在我们已经安装了 Heroku 工具
you can type heroku login and it says "Enter your login credentials",
你可以输入 heroku login 终端显示 "输入你的登录凭证"
email and then it's asking after that for a password.
电子邮件 然后后面会要求输入密码
So, I'm going to hide this from the screen while I put this information in.
为了隐藏这些个人信息 我要将屏幕向上拉一下
Okay. So, now I'm logged into my Heroku account.
好的 现在我登录了我的 Heroku 帐户
Again, it's just a matter of putting in
这步操作只需输入你的 Heroku 帐户的电子邮件和密码即可
Now, there's just some housekeeping to do before we can
现在 只需要再做一些整理工作
upload all of this to a Heroku web server.
就可以将所有内容都上传到 Heroku Web 服务器了
So, first of all, I'm going to open worldbank.py and I'm
首先 打开 worldbank.py
going to remove this app.run line because we don't need this anymore.
删除这个 app.run 代码行 因为我们不再需要它了
I also need to create a Procfile,
我还需要创建一个 Procfile
which is a file that tells Heroku what to do when starting your web app.
这个文件 告诉 Heroku 在启动你的 Web 应用时要做什么
You could do this up here by creating a new file or you can do it in the terminal and say
你可以通过创建新文件来完成此操作 或者可以在终端中执行此操作
touch Procfile and you can see that this Procfile disappeared here in the left hand side.
输入 touch Procfile 你可以看到这个 Procfile 在左侧出现了
I'm going to double click to open it and then I'm going to
双击打开它
say web gunicorn worldbank:app.
输入 web gunicorn worldbank:app
So, this is essentially just says when starting up the web app,
这实际上是指 在启动 Web 应用时
call the gunicorn library and run
调用 gunicorn 库
my worldbank app which has this app variable in it, which we've seen before.
运行我的 worldbank 应用 其中包含这个 app 变量 我们之前看到过
The next thing I need to do is
接下来我需要做的就是
specify all of the Python libraries that are going to be needed.
指定所有需要的 Python 库
So, if you type pip freeze into the terminal,
如果你在终端输入 pip freeze
it's going to give you a list of all of the currently installed Python libraries.
它将为你提供所有当前安装的 Python 库列表
So, you're going to need to put all of
你需要把所有这些信息放入一个名为 requirements.txt 的文件中
So, I'm going to say pip freeze &gt; requirements.txt.
我要输入 pip freeze &gt; requirements.txt
That's going to put all this information into a file called requirements.txt.
这会把所有这些信息放入名为 requirements.txt 的文件中
It's important that this file is actually called
这个文件需要命名为 requirements.txt
requirementstxt because Heroku is going to look for this file.
因为 Heroku 会查找此文件
So, you can see it just lists out all of the Python libraries that this app depends on.
你可以看到其中只是列出了这个应用所依赖的所有 Python 库
The next step is to initiate a git repository.
下一步是初始化一个 git 存储库
So, git init and then git add and then I put the period here.
git init 然后 git add 然后是一个句点
Then I'm going to say git commit -m and say first commit as the message.
然后是 git commit -m 后面加 'first commit' 作为消息
Okay. It says that Please tell me who you are.
终端上显示 请告诉我你是谁
You have to configure an email address and a name.
你必须配置电子邮件地址和用户名
So, you can actually put anything in this that you want.
其实这里可以是任意地址和名称
I'm just going to say something@example.com and git config user.name.
我输入 some@example.com 以及 git config user.name
You can put your real things in here if you want. My name's Andrew.
如果你愿意 你可以放入你的真实信息 我叫 Andrew
So, okay, now let's try committing again,
好的 现在让我们再试一次
git commit -m first commit.
git commit -m 'first commit'
Okay. So, we made our first commit.
好的 我们完成了第一次提交
The last step is to create a web app on Heroku.
最后一步是在 Heroku 上创建一个 Web 应用
So, to do that,
要做到这一点
you say heroku create and then the name of your web app.
输入 heroku create 然后是你的 Web 应用名称
This name has to be distinct.
这个名字必须是唯一的
There can only be one of these names on all of Heroku.
Heroku 上不能出现重复的名称
So, if the first one you try doesn't work,
所以 如果你尝试的第一个名字不行
just keep trying until you find something.
继续努力 直到找到一个不同的名字
So, I'm going to call this dsnd-udacity-webapp.
我打算称之为 dsnd-udacity-webapp
Hit Enter. Okay. So, it gave me the link where I can see the web app,
按回车键 好的 它给了我可以查看该 Web 应用的链接
and then it also created a git repository on
它还在 Heroku 上创建了一个 git 存储库
Heroku where the files are actually going to be uploaded to and stored.
也就是文件实际上传和存储的地方
I'm also, just to double-check,
为了再次确认
I'm going to say git remote -v. Yeah.
我输入 git remote -v
Which shows you that Heroku automatically
终端显示出 Heroku 自动
set up these git repositories as remote repositories for you.
将这些 git 存储库设置为了远程存储库
So, the last step is to say
最后一步就是输入
git push heroku master and that's going to push our app to that Heroku git repository.
git push heroku master 这将把我们的应用推送到 Heroku git 存储库
Okay. Here, it says that everything was deployed to this web address.
这里显示所有内容都部署到了这个网址
So, I'm going to click on that.
我要点击它
Yeah. It looks like the web app deployed.
好 看起来 Web 应用已部署完成了
So, now it's officially at this web address: dsnd-udacity-webapp.herokuapp.com.
现在它的正式网址是 dsnd-udacity-webapp.herokuapp.com
So, that is one way to deploy a Flask app to the web.
这就是将 Flask 应用部署到 Web 的一种方法